<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OD APPLICATION</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>

    <string name="contact"><i><b>Send Us Your Phone Number,\n We Will Contact You.......\n\n</b></i></string>
    <string name="rgukt">
        \n<font fgcolor="#4786be" size="23"><u><b>RGUKT Objectives</b></u></font>\n\n<b>The primary objective of establishing RGUKT was to provide high quality educational opportunities for the aimed rural youth of Andhra Pradesh. The initial goal was that at least the top 1 % of the rural graduates would be given the opportunity to study at RGUKT.</b>
        \n\n<b>The top 1% of rural graduates is around 6,000 to 7,000 per year. Thus, the three campuses would need residential accommodation for about 36,000 students for the six year integrated program.</b>\n\n<font fgcolor="#4786be" size="23"><u><b>Objectives of the University</b></u></font>\n\n
        <b>1.To impart to each student broad skills of Learning to Learn, Learning to Think and Learning to Live.\n\n
    2.To reinforce core values of integrity, respect for all, and care for environment.\n\n
    3.To disseminate and advance knowledge in the emerging fields such as Information Technology, Nanotechnology, etc\.\.\.\n\n
    4.To make special provisions for integrated courses including Humanities, Social Sciences and other interdisciplinary areas to impart broad-based education including soft skills.\n\n
    5.To function as a resource center for knowledge management and entrepreneurship development in the emerging technologies.\n\n
            6.To establish close linkage with industry to make teaching and research at the institutes relevant to the needs of the economy, at national and global levels.\n\n</b>

    </string>
    <string name="home">HOME</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="tgukthome">rgukt</string>
    <string name="help">To get OD Application open the side drawer and click on OD Application. </string>

    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="eroorr">please enter the correct details</string>
    <string name="Help_Questions">
        <b>\n1.How to Apply Original Application?\n</b>
        Ans:- Dear User, Just open the OD Application Tab and fill the all fields to register for
                the Original Degree.
        <b>\n\n2.How to contact us?\n</b>
        Ans:- Dear User, Below the page there will be a option called ContactUs. Select the option
                and Enter your PhoneNumber we will contact you.
        <b>\n\n3.Problem with the Status!\n</b>
        Ans:- The status will be updated, when all details of your\'s are verificed it will be updated
                 the minimum time required is 5 days.\n\n\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="Aboutus_credits">
        \nB.Praneeth\nB.Sushma\nS.Usha\nP.Pushpa\n
    </string>
</resources>
